<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wagging Buddies</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="tnc_shelter">Introduction:
Welcome to Wagging Buddies, a platform dedicated to connecting pet shelters with individuals interested in adopting pets. To ensure the safety and well-being of the animals in your care, and to maintain transparency in our community, we have established the following terms and conditions for shelter registration. By registering your shelter on [Your App Name], you agree to abide by these terms.

1. Shelter Identification:
a. Transparency: The shelter owner must provide accurate and up-to-date information regarding the shelters name, location, contact details, and any relevant licensing or certification.

2. Pet Care Responsibility:
a. Duty of Care: The shelter owner acknowledges that, once a pet is adopted through the app, they assume the responsibility of providing proper care, including shelter, nutrition, medical attention, and love and attention.
b. Adoption Process: The shelter owner agrees to follow responsible adoption procedures, including thorough screening of potential adopters, ensuring the pets suitability for the new home, and providing adequate information about the pets medical history and behavioral traits.

3. Health and Safety:
a. Health Standards: The shelter owner commits to maintaining the health and safety of the pets within their shelter, providing proper vaccinations, medical care, and a clean living environment.
b. Reporting Illness: If any pet in their care displays signs of illness, the shelter owner agrees to promptly seek veterinary care and inform the adopting party.

4. Legal Compliance:
a. Local Laws: The shelter owner agrees to operate in accordance with all local, state, and federal laws related to animal welfare, licensing, and shelter operations.
b. Liability: The shelter owner is solely responsible for any legal or financial liabilities related to their shelter's activities.

5. Accountability:
a. App Accountability: Wagging Buddies reserves the right to hold the shelter owner accountable for any violations of these terms and conditions. This may include removal from the platform or legal action if necessary.

6. Privacy and Data Protection:
a. Data Usage: Wagging Buddies will collect and use data provided by the shelter owner for the purpose of operating the platform and connecting shelters with potential adopters.
b. Data Security: Wagging Buddies is committed to protecting the privacy and security of all user data. The shelter owner agrees to abide by our privacy policy.

7. Amendments and Updates:
a. Review: These terms and conditions may be updated periodically. It is the shelter owner's responsibility to review and comply with the latest version.

8. Termination:
a. Termination: Wagging Buddies reserves the right to terminate a shelter's registration for any reason, including non-compliance with these terms and conditions.

By registering your pet shelter on Wagging Buddies, you acknowledge and agree to these terms and conditions. These terms and conditions form a legally binding agreement between the shelter owner and [Your App Name]. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not proceed with the registration process.</string>
</resources>